Guide to the Curtis Martin Galt Papers, 1922 - 1947
Department of Special Collections
Curtis Martin Galt Papers,
1922 - 1947
Special Collections M0600
Galt, Curtis Martin
2.5 linear ft.
Stanford University. Libraries. Dept. of Special Collections and University Archives.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
None.
Provenance
Gift of the children of the Galts, 1991
Biography
With wife, Mabel Moore Galt, a Presbyterian missionary in Yunnan (China), 1922-1936. Curtis M. Galt returned in 1946-47, to Kun- ming, as superintendent of his fammily Tengchung Hospital.
Scope and Content
Primarily correspondence, some photographs, maps, journals, and Tailu manuscripts.
Access terms
Galt, Mabel Moore, 1898-; Goodenberger, Ernest.; Park, C. Marie.; Presbyterian Church in the U.S.A. Yunnan Mission.; United Nations Relief and Rehabilitation Administration.; Animism--China.; Missionaries.; Tai languages.; Kun-ming shih (China); Yunnan Privince (China)
Container List
- Correspondence: 1923-1924 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Correspondence: 1923 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Correspondence: 1932-1933 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Correspondence: 1931-1933 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Galt Correspondence: 1946 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Galt Correspondence: 1946 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Galt Correspondence: 1946 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Galt Correspondence: 1947 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Miscellaneous: Hymnals (Galt) n.d. (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Galt Correspondence: 1946 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Galt Correspondence: 1946 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Galt Correspondence: 1946 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Galt Correspondence: 1946 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Certificate of Identity and Currency n.d. (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Miscellaneous n.d. (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Photographs n.d. (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Date Book and Miscellaneous n.d. (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Misc: Clippings, photographs, correspondence, maps n.d. (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Financial Papers n.d. (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Misc: photographs, maps n.d. (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Misc: Maps, correspondence n.d. (Box 2, Folder 8)
- "Final Report of Dr. Curtis M. Galt: May 10, 1946 - March 25, 1947" n.d. (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Tai Lu Script n.d. (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Charles E. Park Correspondence: 1943, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Misc: clippings, stories n.d. (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Galt Papers n.d. (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Early Galt Letters to Burkes: 1923-1929 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Galt Correspondence: Sept. 1923 - Dec. 1924 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Galt Correspondence: Jan. 1925 - May 1927 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Galt Correspondence: April 1928 - 1935 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Misc. Galt Papers n.d. (Box 3, Folder 9)
- "The Most Memorable Character I've Met in Yunnan: Mrs. C.E. Park" - C.E. Park n.d. (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Misc. Correspondence, papers n.d. (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Galt Papers (Photocopies) n.d. (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Galt Correspondence: 1925 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Journey through Yunnan, 1935 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Galt - Burkes Correspondence: 1926 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Galt Papers w/ Galt - Burkes Correspondence n.d. (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Galt Papers: "Between San Francisco and Hawaii, Sept. 1923" (Box 3, Folder 17)
- "Biography of Mabel Moore Galt" - C.M. Galt n.d. (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Journals, Diaries, Hymnals (English, Siamese, Chinese) n.d. (Box 4-5)
- UNRRA Hat n.d.